lumoid.com 2017-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Lumoid.com

Hello! Striking Inc. operates the website located at [https://lumoid.com](https://lumoid.com/). This Privacy Policy describes the information that is collected via our website and how that information is used. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please send us an email at [hello@lumoid.com](mailto:hello@lumoid.com). This Privacy Policy also applies to services and products offered by Striking Inc., as well as any other applications, content or features that we may offer from time to time, on our website.

Types of information that we collect

  * We collect information from you, when you subscribe to our newsletter, such as your e-mail address.

  * We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, and respond to communication such as e-mail.

  * When registering with our site, we will ask for your address, email and mailing address, and phone number. In the event we have an issue processing your order, we will use this information to contact you.

  * When placing an order, we will ask for your credit card information.

  * If you contact us via phone, email or through the feedback button on our website, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence.

  * Like a lot of other sites, we use [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) to track visitor trends. This information is anonymous and kept confidential.

  * We use e-mail services such as [MailChimp](http://mailchimp.com/) to send email newsletters to you. MailChimp’s Privacy Policy is located [here](http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

  * Our shopping cart software uses "cookies" to enhance your experience. For more information on how we use cookies, please see below.

  * In any event, we will reserve the right to use your email address and any other personally identifiable information that you provide to us to respond to you, to make recommendations for you and to send you marketing materials for our own products and services.

  * For a limited time period, starting April 1, 2017, Striking, Inc., is partnering with Best Buy Inc. to provide a try before you buy service for various products available on our website. During this time period, we reserve the right to share with Best Buy, personally identifiable information, including but not limited to, email address, shipping information and phone number, for the users participating in this trial, and visiting the website via Best Buy's website.

Cookies and Online Tracking

Like most websites, our website may incorporate "pixel tags", or similar tracking technologies and “cookies” that allow us to track the actions of visitors of our website. Pixel tags and cookies are used to collect non-personally identifiable information, such as the name of your internet service provider, the IP address of the computer you are using, the type of browser software and operating system that is used, the date and time you access our website, the website address, if any, from which you linked directly to our website, the website address, if any, to which you travel from our website, your home page customization preferences and any other similar traffic-related information. We may also aggregate your information with similar data collected from other visitors to help us improve our website and the products, services, applications, content and features that we provide via our website. We do not make use of non-personally identifiable information in any way to create or maintain a personal profile of you or collect personally identifiable information from you.

How the information we gather is used

We will generally not disclose the personally identifiable information that we collect through your use of our website to unaffiliated third parties. We reserve the right, however, to provide such information to our employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform services on our behalf, including order fulfillment and website-related services such as web hosting, to improve website-related services and features, to perform maintenance services, and to distribute advertisements and other marketing materials on our behalf. We reserve the right to use the information to process your transactions, and to track your order history so that we may answer any recommendations or concerns, and to send you newsletters and provide information on services that we think will be of interest to you. We also reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable information that we collect to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following reasons: (i) to comply with the law; (ii) to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect, or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of our website or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, safety and security of Striking Inc. and its employees, our website visitors, and/or the public.

For a limited time period, starting April 1, 2017, Striking, Inc., is partnering with Best Buy Inc. to provide a try before you buy service for various products available on our website. During this time period, we reserve the right to share with Best Buy, personally identifiable information, including but not limited to, email address, shipping information and phone number, for the users participating in this trial, and visiting the website via Best Buy's website.

Protecting your information

All of the information that we collect about our customers is stored on secure servers, reachable only through secure networks. Your order is transmitted via [SSL](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security), and is stored in an encrypted format on our servers. Our physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards meet or exceed current federal standards regarding the protection of customer information. We also require contractors and outside companies who work with us to adhere to strict privacy standards through their contractual agreements with us. Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and our servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the website. Any information that you provide to us is done so entirely at your own risk.

Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?

No. We will never give your information to anyone, for any reason. There are a few exceptions. We may need to provide your information to our hosting partners, and other parties that help us in managing our business (such as our merchant gateway). These parties must be required to keep your information confidential. There may be cases where we are required by law to provide your information to law enforcement.

For a limited time period, starting April 1, 2017, Striking, Inc., is partnering with Best Buy Inc. to provide a try before you buy service for various products available on our website. During this time period, we reserve the right to share with Best Buy, personally identifiable information, including but not limited to, email address, shipping information and phone number, for the users participating in this trial, and visiting the website via Best Buy's website.

Opting Out

If at any time you would like to change your personally identifiable information, no longer wish to receive materials from us or would like your personal information removed from our database, please contact us at [hello@lumoid.com](mailto:hello@lumoid.com). If you would like to unsubscribe, please use the the "unsubscribe" function in all our email communications with you so that we know that you no longer wish to receive any materials from us.

We reserve the right to update and revise this privacy policy

From time to time we review this Privacy Policy to ensure that it complies with applicable law. Consequently, we reserve the right to update and revise this Privacy Policy at any time. Updates to the privacy policy will be posted on www.lumoid.com.

Questions and feedback

Please contact us by email if you have any questions at [hello@lumoid.com](mailto:hello@lumoid.com)

Online Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Business Partnerships and Data Transfer

If we sell all or any part of our business, or sell or transfer all or a material part of our assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or other transfer or disposition of any part our business, we reserve the right to access, transfer or disclose any and all information that we collect from our website’s visitors, or that we otherwise collect in connection with the website, to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

Our website may contain links to other websites

Please be aware that we are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any websites that you access through our website and that this Privacy Policy applies solely to the information which we collect through our website. We encourage you to ensure that you read the privacy statements of all the destination websites which you visit.

Your consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
